<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Pro Bono &#8211; Group CJ Lexington Kentucky</title>
	<atom:link href="/portfolio_category/pro-bono/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 18:54:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>Keep Lexington Beautiful</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/keep-lexington-beautiful/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 16:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.9.29/Development/TB/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission’s mission is to engage our citizens to protect and improve Lexington’s environment through personal responsibility. We unite citizens, businesses and government to find solutions that advance our core issues of preventing litter, reducing waste, and beautifying communities. The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission is not a government entity. It is a group of benevolent corporate citizens and volunteers.&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/keep-lexington-beautiful/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission</b><b>’s </b>mission is to engage our citizens to protect and improve Lexington’s environment through personal responsibility. We unite citizens, businesses and government to find solutions that advance our core issues of preventing litter, reducing waste, and beautifying communities.</p>
<p>The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission is not a government entity. It is a group of benevolent corporate citizens and volunteers. Yearly, the Group CJ and the Commission host several educational and environmental events in addition to the multiple events surrounding the Great American Cleanup (March-May): The annual litter survey in which sections of the city are measured and rated according to their pollution levels (March); the CLPP Cigarette Litter Prevention program and materials (ongoing); Wolf Run Watershed Management Project and educational festival (October); and America Recycles Day/Recycle Bowl (November). To learn more about The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission, visit their website at <a href="http://www.keeplexingtonbeautiful.com/" target="_blank">www.KeepLexingtonBeautiful.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Downtown Lexington Corporation</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/downtown-lexington-corporation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 15:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wellingtonarmslexington.com/groupcj2/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Group CJ works with the Downtown Lexington Corporation  to raise local awareness of the importance of a thriving downtown to the economic vitality of the city. We revamped their logo and brand in 2012 to capitalize on the excitement of the new booming culinary scene and announcement of the 21C hotel coming to downtown. [mejsvideo src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/DLC-GoDowntown-30TV.mp4" width="348" height="288"]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Group CJ works with the Downtown Lexington Corporation  to raise local awareness of the importance of a thriving downtown to the economic vitality of the city. We revamped their logo and brand in 2012 to capitalize on the excitement of the new booming culinary scene and announcement of the 21C hotel coming to downtown.</p>
<p><center>[mejsvideo src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/DLC-GoDowntown-30TV.mp4" width="348" height="288"]</center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bluegrass Conservancy</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/the-bluegrass-conservancy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 13:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wellingtonarmslexington.com/groupcj2/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Founded in 1995, Bluegrass Conservancy is an accredited, private, nonprofit land trust working to protect the Inner Bluegrass Region of Kentucky through land conservation for future generations through the use of conservation easements for agricultural viability, natural habitat, rural heritage, and scenic open space.  To date, 100 parcels encompassing approximately 18,452 acres have been conserved. Connie Jo Miller, board member, and&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/the-bluegrass-conservancy/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Founded in 1995, Bluegrass Conservancy is an accredited, private, nonprofit land trust working to protect the Inner Bluegrass Region of Kentucky through land conservation for future generations through the use of conservation easements for agricultural viability, natural habitat, rural heritage, and scenic open space.  To date, 100 parcels encompassing approximately 18,452 acres have been conserved.</p>
<p>Connie Jo Miller, board member, and Group CJ assist the Conservancy annually with their collateral and fundraising material and annual events.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lexarts</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/lexarts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 16:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.9.29/Development/TB/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When the Lexington Arts and Cultural Council decided to become LexArts, Group CJ created the organization’s new visual identity. The campaign that unveiled the new identity raised over $1 million. And the design received numerous awards from the American Advertising Federation’s Lexington Advertising Club. Group CJ was actively involved in all aspects of a recent LexArts Ball, from invitation design&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/lexarts/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the Lexington Arts and Cultural Council decided to become LexArts, Group CJ created the organization’s new visual identity. The campaign that unveiled the new identity raised over $1 million. And the design received numerous awards from the American Advertising Federation’s Lexington Advertising Club.</p>
<p>Group CJ was actively involved in all aspects of a recent LexArts Ball, from invitation design to décor to sponsorship solicitation. The 2007 Midsummer Masquerade LexArts Ball, sponsored by 34 companies, saw an 100% increase in attendance and $36,100 in Ball revenue was eligible for Mayor’s Challenge matching funds raising even more for LexArts. Group CJ has also been actively involved in Horse Mania and the LexArts annual fundraising events.</p>
<p><center>[mejsvideo src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/newLexarts.m4v" width="348" height="288"]</center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
