<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>City/Environmental &#8211; Group CJ Lexington Kentucky</title>
	<atom:link href="/portfolio_category/city-and-environmental/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 16:43:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>&#8220;Safer Streets&#8221;: Public Awareness Bicyclists &#038; Pedestrian Safety</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/public-awareness-bicyclists-pedestrian-safety/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 14:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=3284</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Background According to Kentucky’s official annual collision report, there were over 1,000 collisions with pedestrians and 495 with bicyclists – accounting for about 10% of all collision fatalities. Some of the highest factors noted in this report were ‘inattention’, ‘failing to yield’ and ‘distraction’. As Lexington grows more and more miles of bike lanes and ped-friendly infrastructure, and technology grows&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/public-awareness-bicyclists-pedestrian-safety/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Background<br />
According to Kentucky’s official annual collision report, there were over 1,000 collisions with pedestrians and 495 with bicyclists – accounting for about 10% of all collision fatalities. Some of the highest factors noted in this report were ‘inattention’, ‘failing to yield’ and ‘distraction’. As Lexington grows more and more miles of bike lanes and ped-friendly infrastructure, and technology grows increasingly mobile - it’s paramount that shine a light on safety and congestion mitigation.</p>
<p>Challenge<br />
Develop an attention-getting, behavior changing, street smart campaign. A multi-media communications effort aimed at changing behavior and creating more mindful community out on the streets. The messaging will educate Lexingtonians how to stay safe and avoid traffic accidents. Increased safety = increased alternative transportation (biking, walking) = better air quality and a healthier environment.</p>
<p><center><iframe loading="lazy" src="//player.vimeo.com/video/159808518" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></center></p>
<p><
</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lexington Fayette County Health Department</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/lexington-fayette-county-health-department/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 19:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=3263</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From H1N1, to colon cancer awareness, to "Third Hand Smoke", Group CJ is always quick to lend a hand when it comes to the health of our community.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From H1N1, to colon cancer awareness, to "Third Hand Smoke", Group CJ is always quick to lend a hand when it comes to the health of our community.</p>
<p><center><iframe loading="lazy" src="//player.vimeo.com/video/155394864" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>City of Lexington: Division of Environmental Services</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/department-of-environmental-quality/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 16:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.9.29/Development/TB/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=521</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Situation: When the EPA sued Lexington for violating the Clean Water Act, it left the city’s newly-created Department of Environmental Services with a daunting list of EPA-mandated projects. They needed a responsive agency accustomed to getting up to speed on complex issues. Hot Idea: Lexington needed to know why - and how - its water quality was going down the storm drain.&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/department-of-environmental-quality/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><span style="color: #000000;">Situation:</span></strong> When the EPA sued Lexington for violating the Clean Water Act, it left the city’s newly-created Department of Environmental Services with a daunting list of EPA-mandated projects. They needed a responsive agency accustomed to getting up to speed on complex issues.</p>
<p><strong><span style="color: #000000;">Hot Idea:</span></strong> Lexington needed to know why - and how - its water quality was going down the storm drain. So we launched a campaign of TV and print ads which really grabbed people’s attention. Especially since we seriously worked our media connections to beef up our media budget with a flood of bonus spots.</p>
<p><strong><span style="color: #000000;">Cool Results:</span></strong> We helped launch a new city-wide awareness of green issues with intrusive creative and an extra boost: almost-triple negotiated broadcast exposure and significant press coverage. And the added bonus of an integrated brand capable of accommodating Department of Environmental Services consumer communications about green issues from water to waste.</p>
<p><center><iframe loading="lazy" src="//player.vimeo.com/video/114269517" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></center><div class="span4 "><div class="title-box clearfix Testimonial #4 DEQ"><h2 class="title-box_primary"></h2></div><!-- //.title-box --> <div class="testimonials"><div class="testi-item"><blockquote class="testi-item_blockquote"><a href="/testimonial-view/testimonial-4-deq/">Group CJ has demonstrated great excitement for our Live Green Lexington project. Their creativity and enthusiasm has been simply outstanding and clearly visible in the products they have provided for our campaign.  ... </a><div class="clear"></div></blockquote><small class="testi-meta"><span class="user">Mark York</span>, <span class="info">Environmental Quality Outreach and Education</span><br></small></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Move It People</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/move-it-people/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 07:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://livedemo00.template-help.com/wordpress_44406/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=1907</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Situation: Nationwide, cities are learning that more public awareness will increase alterative transportation and public support. The benefits are astounding. Alternative transportation, walking, biking, mass transit, not only have an effect on the health of our bodies and environment, but plays a large part in the vitality of our city and quality of life. The case for public transportation is&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/move-it-people/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Situation:</strong> Nationwide, cities are learning that more public awareness will increase alterative transportation and public support. The benefits are astounding. Alternative transportation, walking, biking, mass transit, not only have an effect on the health of our bodies and environment, but plays a large part in the vitality of our city and quality of life. The case for public transportation is indisputable: For every $1 dollar invested in public transportation, the community generates $4. But…what have we Americans been raised to revere almost as much as mom and apple pie? Our Chevys.</p>
<p><strong>Hot Idea:</strong> We decided it was time for Lexington to start behaving the next Great American City it’s poised to become. Our strategy was to pool campaign funds from entities who have common goals. It just makes strategic sense to unite folks who run the trolleys, plan the parking and encourage us to think outside of the car every once and while.</p>
<p>Our common platform is a hip new movement called Move It People, which is comprised of a complex, hard-hitting media campaign, social media, website, mass transit and environmental graphics.</p>
<p><strong>Cool Results:</strong> We got the message out loud and clear to our community that it’s time to be urban cool, think green by biking, walking, and using mass transit.</p>
<p><center><iframe loading="lazy" src="//player.vimeo.com/video/112946708" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Keep Lexington Beautiful</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/keep-lexington-beautiful/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 16:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.9.29/Development/TB/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission’s mission is to engage our citizens to protect and improve Lexington’s environment through personal responsibility. We unite citizens, businesses and government to find solutions that advance our core issues of preventing litter, reducing waste, and beautifying communities. The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission is not a government entity. It is a group of benevolent corporate citizens and volunteers.&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/keep-lexington-beautiful/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission</b><b>’s </b>mission is to engage our citizens to protect and improve Lexington’s environment through personal responsibility. We unite citizens, businesses and government to find solutions that advance our core issues of preventing litter, reducing waste, and beautifying communities.</p>
<p>The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission is not a government entity. It is a group of benevolent corporate citizens and volunteers. Yearly, the Group CJ and the Commission host several educational and environmental events in addition to the multiple events surrounding the Great American Cleanup (March-May): The annual litter survey in which sections of the city are measured and rated according to their pollution levels (March); the CLPP Cigarette Litter Prevention program and materials (ongoing); Wolf Run Watershed Management Project and educational festival (October); and America Recycles Day/Recycle Bowl (November). To learn more about The Keep Lexington Beautiful Commission, visit their website at <a href="http://www.keeplexingtonbeautiful.com/" target="_blank">www.KeepLexingtonBeautiful.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kentucky Department Of Agriculture</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/kentucky-department-of-agriculture/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 16:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.9.29/Development/TB/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=517</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Situation: As Kentucky actively sought to diversify away from tobacco, the promotion of alternative crops became more vital than ever. That is why the Kentucky Department of Agriculture turned to Group CJ to launch a unified marketing and advertising campaign for Kentucky’s unbranded farm products on a limited budget of $300,000. Hot Idea: A survey of 8,000 Kentucky consumers, showed&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/kentucky-department-of-agriculture/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Situation:</strong> As Kentucky actively sought to diversify away from tobacco, the promotion of alternative crops became more vital than ever. That is why the Kentucky Department of Agriculture turned to Group CJ to launch a unified marketing and advertising campaign for Kentucky’s unbranded farm products on a limited budget of $300,000.</p>
<p><strong>Hot Idea:</strong> A survey of 8,000 Kentucky consumers, showed “freshness” to be the number one motivation in food-buying decisions. Based on this research, the CJ team developed a communication strategy based on the idea of “Kentucky Fresh”.  The campaign slogan: <b><i>“Taste Kentucky Fresh. Nothing Else is Close.”</i></b> reinforced the message that buying local means buying fresh.</p>
<p>Kentucky Fresh ads brought the taste of Kentucky produce to the forefront with the sound of freshness. The echo of an actual bite into locally grown corn on the cob, the slurp of a fresh Kentucky peach and the snap of a bean. We produced lively and attention-getting television commercials that spoke to the consumer.</p>
<p><strong>Cool Results:</strong> Kentucky Fresh/Kentucky Proud was embraced by the farmer and consumer largely due to the efforts of Group CJ. Our grass roots strategy paid off as increasing consumer demand for “local Kentucky” produce prompted retailers to actively seek local suppliers to fulfill this demand.</p>
<p>Partly in response to consumer demand, Kentucky Fresh/Kentucky Proud branded products made their debut in Wal-Mart stores in Central Kentucky. And today, you’ll see Kentucky Fresh/Kentucky Proud at almost every outdoor market, in many restaurants and grocery stores.</p>
<p><strong>A combination of hard work and our excellent media relationships enabled us to ultimately report a 65% increase in the total budget through documented value-added exposure! That truly is what we are known for - maximizing every penny.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lexpark</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/lexpark/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 16:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.9.29/Development/TB/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=514</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Situation: Accessible and safe parking structures are vital to a vibrant city center.  Difficulty in finding parking was keeping shoppers and diners circling our streets and staying away from downtown. Faced with the prospect of increased enforcement and rising costs, the LFUCG brought Group CJ on board. Our charge - to brand and create a communications plan for LexPark, and&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/lexpark/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Situation: </strong>Accessible and safe parking structures are vital to a vibrant city center.  Difficulty in finding parking was keeping shoppers and diners circling our streets and staying away from downtown. Faced with the prospect of increased enforcement and rising costs, the LFUCG brought Group CJ on board. Our charge - to brand and create a communications plan for LexPark, and its new parking structure designed to make downtown more user-friendly.</p>
<p><strong>Hot Idea: </strong>Parking being a traditionally sensitive subject, it was important not to ruffle any feathers. We approached the project with an upbeat attitude and created a user friendly look.</p>
<p><strong>Cool Results:</strong> We launched a multi media campaign to let people know that parking was widely available downtown, as well as convenient and cost-effective.</p>
<p><span style="color: #00ccff;"><strong>Lexpark Social Success Story: Friend the parking people? Seriously?</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">In March 2013 Group CJ demonstrated to the Lexington Parking Authority Board of Commissioners that they quite a prolific presence on Facebook where citizens were busily sharing their opinions about LEXPARK. The activity was so widespread that there was not one, but four sites dedicated to LEXPARK.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Unfortunately the four sites included “Say no to LEXPARK” and “F*CK LEXPARK” and there in fact was no official site for Authority. At first a skeptical Authority doubted whether citizens would respond – a very natural response seeing most people friend family, sports teams and their beloved personal favorite brands. But they made the bold move and the story unfolded quickly and more positively than anyone imagined.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Four months later 1,000 people have signed up as LEXPARK friends allowing the Authority to reach 30,000 people per week through their extended friend network. Regular posts have started the process of shaking the negative image many have of the Authority by showing how parking is free after 5PM and that parking fees have now renovated once dangerous city garages and brought to the social world the exciting and advanced new “Helix” garage. The point was made that even something as seemingly unlovable as a parking authority has a good story to tell and if they don’t tell it, others will.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Social media has allowed citizens to get engaged and interested in what the Authority does and then in turn have allowed natural digital word-of-mouth to spread the good things LEXPARK is doing.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LEXserv City Services</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/lexserv/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 07:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://livedemo00.template-help.com/wordpress_44406/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=1904</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Situation: Lexington residents and businesses would soon be getting their water quality management, sewer and landfill fees in a separate bill. Kentucky American Water, who previously included the charges for these services in the water bill, decided to end the billing and collections contracts with the city of Lexington. As if explaining how to pay this new bill wasn’t enough,&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/lexserv/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Situation:</strong> Lexington residents and businesses would soon be getting their water quality management, sewer and landfill fees in a separate bill. Kentucky American Water, who previously included the charges for these services in the water bill, decided to end the billing and collections contracts with the city of Lexington. As if explaining how to pay this new bill wasn’t enough, it also brought attention to the fees for city services that may have been overlooked until now. And if just 10% of the community failed to pay the bill, the city had the potential to lose over 6 million dollars.</p>
<p><strong>Hot Idea:</strong> Awareness, smart positioning and recognition of the new city bill were key. Group CJ, working closely with consultants, environmental quality, focus groups and the Division of Revenue, crafted a simple, hard hitting campaign that included mass media, direct mail, digital media and PR. Our approach was to let the community know what exactly their fees pay for - the somewhat progressive services that our city provides. And of course, remind them subtly that if they did not pay, there would be consequences.</p>
<p><strong>Cool Results:</strong> The campaign launched with little pushback and a lot of bills being paid. In fact, the response was so overwhelming - people paying in person at City Hall - that the city decided to install and easy-pay drop box right on Main. Operationally, the transition was pretty seamless - partly due to the fact that we prefaced the change with landlords and began the campaign early with the right amount of reach and frequency.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Downtown Lexington Corporation</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/downtown-lexington-corporation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 15:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wellingtonarmslexington.com/groupcj2/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Group CJ works with the Downtown Lexington Corporation  to raise local awareness of the importance of a thriving downtown to the economic vitality of the city. We revamped their logo and brand in 2012 to capitalize on the excitement of the new booming culinary scene and announcement of the 21C hotel coming to downtown. [mejsvideo src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/DLC-GoDowntown-30TV.mp4" width="348" height="288"]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Group CJ works with the Downtown Lexington Corporation  to raise local awareness of the importance of a thriving downtown to the economic vitality of the city. We revamped their logo and brand in 2012 to capitalize on the excitement of the new booming culinary scene and announcement of the 21C hotel coming to downtown.</p>
<p><center>[mejsvideo src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/DLC-GoDowntown-30TV.mp4" width="348" height="288"]</center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lexington Tax Amnesty</title>
		<link>/portfolio-view/tax-amnesty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nancy@groupcj.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 16:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.9.29/Development/TB/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=519</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Situation: The Lexington-Fayette Urban County Government needed help in recovering unpaid net profit and payroll taxes. They turned to Group CJ. Hot Idea: Our solution was to use a carrot and stick strategy – coupling an incentive to act with a reminder of the consequences of non-compliance. The message, “pay now or pay more later” was conveyed in high-frequency, high-impact&#160;<a href="/portfolio-view/tax-amnesty/" class="read-more">Continue Reading</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Situation:</strong> The Lexington-Fayette Urban County Government needed help in recovering unpaid net profit and payroll taxes. They turned to Group CJ.</p>
<p><strong>Hot Idea: </strong>Our solution was to use a carrot and stick strategy – coupling an incentive to act with a reminder of the consequences of non-compliance. The message, “pay now or pay more later” was conveyed in high-frequency, high-impact TV, radio and print executions. Group CJ coupled that with good public relations and added value/bonus spots thanks to our long-standing stellar relationships with the local media.</p>
<p><strong>Cool Results:</strong> A $100,000 investment reaped $2.9 million in additional revenue for the city – ten times what the Mayor expected. Long-term benefits included the addition of 1,250 new taxpayers to the collection rolls.</p>
<p>After witnessing the results of Lexington’s Tax Amnesty, the City of Covington asked Group CJ to do the same, which was held in the spring of 2004 and collected over $375,000.</p>
<p>And we did it again in 2010. Group CJ launched a Tax Amnesty campaign in three short weeks recovering over $1,700,000 in unpaid taxes.</p>
<p>For the effort, Group CJ successfully walked away with the only Tall Addy for Documented Sales Success in 2010.</p>
<p><center>[mejsvideo src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/TA30A.mp4" width="348" height="288"]</center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
